# **Connor Ruthven**

#### (916) 607-0646

#### connorruthven@gmail.com

### **Summary**

Highly motivated individual that is actively acquiring new skills via continuing education. Currently enrolled in courses that help me develop highly sought after technical skills. Excel in being personable, patient, and having a strong "can-do" attitude towards problems. Passionate about research and creating things from scratch.

## **Skills**

**Environments**: macOS, Windows, Linux

**Browsers**: Chrome, Safari, Firefox

Languages: CSS/HTML, Javascript (MERN stack), Python, Powershell, Git

Management: , Excel, MongoDB

Other: MS Office Suite 2000+ (Excel, Word, PowerPoint), Google

Workspace, Slack, Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator, Bootstrap,

¡Query, Agile software development methodology

#### **Experience**

Raley's / BelAir, 523 - Courtesy Clerk August 2018 - June 2021

Food Service Deli Clerk June 2021 - Present

- Superior customer service skills and able to communicate effectively with diverse individuals/populations
- Great attention to detail in handling and processing transactions as well as placing inventory purchase orders
- Maintained Safety and Sanitation standards throughout the business
- Excellent at organizing/maintaining store appearance and inventory

• Easily adaptable when given additional responsibilities and able to utilize appropriate time management skills

 Consistent record keeping and reviewing/correcting important information to maintain accurate records

• Ability to work independently while multitasking in a fast-paced environment

• Easily picked up technology that is necessary to perform job duties such as using pointof-sale systems and other technology

• Facilitated interviews and assisted with job training for new hires

• Understanding protocols regarding customers and maintenance tasks (especially in relation to Covid-19)

• Maintaining a dialogue to satisfy customers to help give them an experience of feeling cared about and valued

## **Education**

Elk Grove High School Class of 2018

Elk Grove, CA - High School Diploma

**Cosumnes River College** 

Sacramento, CA - In progress ...

**UC Davis Coding Bootcamp** December 2023 - Current

Fullstack web development training program.

References available upon request